Friends, now you tell me that you
all will be safe. I am in Kota. A little bit about that,
friends, the
health insurance policy of the people in their homes,
transferred online through your
credit card, it does not depend on doing anything, if they have to
request payment in their vote bank, whether it is a cheque payment
or a question, then it does not do so due to some reasons. I
request all of you
if you have body pimple meeting then you
can do it online and
you have to do it online,
if I request you from the previous one and
hence you will find out so that your benefits will remain with
you. Thank you, if
you get some online payment
then call me, I will click
and tell you how you want to make online payment. There is
no such disease in the accused.
In an exam, sometimes a teacher,
if any person is treated by Azhar Muslim,
then on the other hand, but if any
person is going to a private hospital, then
his order is also medical test in the final
admission, waiting and today's news lead to the
person  Skin black printed in a private hospital, it
cost 16 lakh rupees that
you should make good preparations in your life,
then you should
find out what life is like for your family, pimples, and you feel that there is
tension and but wait a bit, then you
must comment me and if you have
taken it till now, then I have
given the contact number in the description, you can call me and tell me
that it is very important for you and your
family to have a tricolor, because
in the accused
you came to know that grocery processing is necessary,
fuel soon they will definitely buy mini bus, this is definitely
meat, but if you have ever thought till now
or that you like, like, comment, share is
necessary, you want to add it to your family, then
definitely do it now and if you liked this video, then
definitely share it with your friend or relative, if you meet
there, definitely share it with them.